crockpot365.blogspot.com 2019-10-22

# Terms of Agreement and Privacy Policy - Stephanie ODea

This policy agreement encompasses stephanieodea.com, ayearofslowcooking.com,  themommybloggernextdoor, glutenfreesearchengine.com, and simpleshortcutstopeace.com as entities of the O’Dea Media Group, LLC.

**General Statement About Privacy:**  
The websites (stephanieodea.com, ayearofslowcooking.com, themommybloggernextdoor.com, glutenfreesearchengine.com, and simpleshortcutstopeace.com) are committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This policy outlines what information may be collected when you visit the sites, and how that information is used. When you continue to visit the websites, you are consenting to the practices described in this policy.

The O’Dea Media Group, LLC believes very strongly in keeping your personal information confidential.  The following policy describes what information we collect and how it is used and shared.

**Information Collected**  
O’Dea Media Group, LLC collects as little information as possible from users looking to post comments and messages in the forum.  We will typically collect a name (either real or alias), personal website, and e-mail address.

**Cookies / IP Address tracking**  
O’Dea Media Group, LLC uses cookies to uniquely identify users for the purpose of log files, posting comments, and voting on the site.  No personal information is stored in these cookies and it simply a way to identify your computer.

**With Whom Information is Shared**  
None of your information will be shared with third parties.  O’Dea Media Group may use your e-mail address in the future to contact you regarding the site, however, an opt-out will always be provided.  Your name and website may be displayed on the site if you post a comment or a message in the forum.  However, your e-mail address and privacy will always be kept secure.

**Opting Out**  
If O’Dea Media Group, LLC chooses to send out newsletter updates in the future and we have your email address on file, you may receive a copy of our newsletter.  However, at the bottom of every newsletter will be an easy way to opt-out.  The editors of our site hate SPAM as much as you and have no intention of filling up e-mail boxes with unwanted messages.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

**SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION**

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to the included Websites. This includes your social security number, information regarding race or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

**CHILDREN’S INFORMATION**

The included Websites do not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at contact@stephanieodea.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Use of Affiliate Networks:

The O’Dea Media Group, LLC is a member of Amazon Affiliate and Amazon Influencer network.  If an item is recommended for purchase and is available through Amazon, an affiliate link will be used. When you purchase an item through such a link, the O’Dea Media Group, LLC will receive a small portion of the sale, at no further cost to you.

#### FTC Publishing Guidelines:

The O’Dea Media Group, LLC adheres to the rules outlined by the [FTC (Federal Trade Commission)](http://www.ftc.gov/opa/2009/10/endortest.shtm) and will always disclose when a product or item has been given free of charge for review and/or giveaway and when/if the recommendation is a paid endorsement.

#### If you have any questions about this policy please contact contact (at) stephanieodea (dot) com

**Changes to This Policy:**  
We reserve the right to update or change this privacy policy at any time. Any such change, modification, or addition to the privacy policy on stephanieodea.com, ayearofslowcooking.com, themommybloggernextdoor.com, glutenfreesearchengine.com, and simpleshortcutstopeace.com will become effective immediately upon posting on the sites.

If you have any questions whatsoever about this Privacy Policy, please contact the website owner at contact@stephanieodea.com

This policy was last updated in May, 2018
